indoleads.com 2019-12-24

# Indoleads.com - Privacy Policy |

## Effective Date: 01/09/2015

Thank you for visiting the Indoleads.com affiliate network website located at indoleads.com (the “Site”). Indoleads.com (“we”, “us”) is committed to protecting the privacy your personally identifiable information. We provide this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) in order to explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is used by us. You must agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, including our use of cookies in order to: register an account (“Account”) with the Indoleads.com affiliate network (“Affiliate Network”) and log-into your Account as member of the Affiliate Network. Your acceptance of both this Privacy Policy and our use of cookies on the Site shall be deemed a blanket acceptance of such Privacy Policy and cookie usage for all future attempts to log-in and access your Account. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety, you are not authorized to register for an Account on the Affiliate Network.

## Privacy Policies Used in Connection with Your Subscription.

When you register for an Account on the Affiliate Net work, we use a password-protected third party portal to store your personal information, and we may share your personal information with such third party (“Third Party Agent”) as is necessary for the performance of your Account and the Affiliate Network.

## Personally Identifiable Information.

We collect personally identifiable information when you register for an Account or otherwise choose to provide personally identifiable information to us. Personally identifiable information is any information that can be used to identify or locate a particular person or entity. This may include, but is not limited to: business entity name and/or your title with the applicable business entity, as well as your personal and/or business entity related e-mail address, mailing address, daytime and/or cellular telephone numbers, fax number, account information (or other information that we require in order to pay any amounts due to you under the Affiliate Network) and/or any other information requested on the applicable Subscriber registration form. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, your account information shall be considered “Sensitive Information.”

## Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you when you visit certain pages of this Site and/or register for an Account on the Affiliate Network, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows ’98 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink), and share such information with our Third Party Agent. We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of the Site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze Site usage.

## End User Information.

We do not collect personally identifiable information about your end users. However, we do use cookies to track anonymous traffic data about your end users. When end users who visit member affiliate sites click on the advertisement(s) they have chosen to display through their Accounts on the Affiliate Network, we will utilize cookies and/or web beacons to track such end users activities at our merchant site(s). In certain circumstances, we may use cookie-less tracking methods to track such end users.

## Use of Information.

We use your personally identifiable information: (a) to send you information regarding your Account and the Affiliate Network; (b) to track your compliance with the Terms and Conditions (“Terms and Conditions”); and/or (c) for validation, suppression, content improvement and feedback purposes. You agree that we, or our Third Party Agent, may contact you at any time with updates and/or any other information that we may deem appropriate for you to receive in connection with your Account on the Affiliate Network.

## Information Sharing.

As a general rule, and other than in connection with the limited exceptions set forth below, we will not sell, share or rent your personally identifiable information to or with others. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may, from time to time, provide such information to certain third-party administrative vendors for efficiency purposes in providing administrative or program management services in connection with your Account. Any third-party vendor so used has agreed to protect the confidentiality of information provided by us.  
Further, we reserve the right to share your personally identifiable information: (a) where required by law, or requested by a court of competent jurisdiction; (b) in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock; (c) where you are in violation of this Privacy Policy, the Terms and Conditions and/or Services Agreement; (d) in the case of a dispute; or (e) where we determine, in our sole discretion, that such disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or a third party, or necessary to protect us from liability of any kind. The aforementioned includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

## International Transfer of Data.

As part of your membership in the Affiliate Network, we may transfer information that we collect about you and your end users, including personal information, to affiliated entities, or to other third parties across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you or your end users are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring information and permitting the transfer of information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction. You consent to the transfer of your information to the United States and the use and disclosure of information about you and your end users, including personal information, as described in this Privacy Policy.

## Data Retention.

Subject to any mandatory obligations to delete data, your information may be retained by us and in our Third Party Agent portal, server logs, databases and records indefinitely.

## Third Party Links.

The Site may contain links to third-party websites (“Third Party Websites”). Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of Third Party Websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Site and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Site.

## Your Employees.

Your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy, in their entirety, shall extend to your employees, if any. You agree that any of your employees that access your Account, or visit the Site under the scope of their employment with you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

## Minors.

We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children. We will never knowingly collect any personal information about individuals under eighteen (18) years of age. If we obtain actual knowledge that it we have collected personal information about an individual under eighteen (18) years of age, that information will be immediately deleted from its database.

## Security.

We endeavor to safeguard and protect our Account holders’ information. When Account holders submit personally identifiable information to the Affiliate Network, their personally identifiable information is protected both online and offline. When our registration process asks registrants to submit Sensitive Information (such as bank account information and/or credit card information), and when we transmit such Sensitive Information, that Sensitive Information is encrypted and protected with SSL encryption software. While we use SSL encryption to protect Sensitive Information online, we protect all other user information online and offline. The Third Party Agent servers that we utilize to store personally identifiable information in are kept in a secure physical environment. The Third Party Agent has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of personally identifiable information stored on its servers.

Please be advised that, although we take every reasonable precaution available to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through our Site is at your own risk. However, access to your personally identifiable information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. Only employees, and third party agents, that need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all user information. Employees not adhering to our written firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personally identifiable information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.

You acknowledge that you provide your personally identifiable information to us with knowledgeable consent and at your own risk.

## Deleting and Updating Your Information.

If you would like to delete or update the personally identifiable information that we have collected from you, simply email us at: publishers@indoleads.com.  
We will process your request, where possible and subject to the terms and conditions contained herein, within a reasonable period of time after receipt. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

## Opting Out of Receiving E-mail.

You may at any time choose to stop receiving emails containing general information regarding Indoleads.com by following the instructions at the end of each such email or by contacting us at publishers@indoleads.com. Should you be contacted by our Third Party Agent through email, you can follow the instructions at the end of each such email to stop receiving such emails. There may be a short delay of up to several business days while your request is being verified, deployed and processed across our servers. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to your Account, as well as to respond to any inquiry or request made by you.

## Notification of Changes.

We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a clear and conspicuous notice on the Site explaining that we are changing our Privacy Policy. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site. Please check the Site periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site and/or acceptance of our e-mail communications following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes.

## Contact Us.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us at: care@indoleads.com

## Exhibit A  
More about cookies on indoleads.com

Using indoleads.com requires the use of cookies. If you have do not want to accept the cookies for indoleads.com or from any of our third parties, you won’t be able to use our service.

We use a cookie to remember your cookie preferences this has a couple of consequences:

If you delete all your cookies you will have to update your preferences with us again.

If you use a different device, computer profile or browser you will have to tell us your preferences again.

The cookies used on indoleads.com are based on the International Chamber of Commerce guide for cookie categories:

## Strictly necessary  
Performance  
Functionality  
For more information about cookies see the  
Further Reading link below.

‘Strictly Necessary’ cookies let you move around the website and login to your secure account. These cookies don’t gather any information about you that could be used for marketing or remembering where you’ve been on the internet.

## We use these Strictly Necessary cookies to…

Identify you as being logged in to indoleads.com  
Remember things like information you’ve entered on forms when you navigate to different pages in a single web browser session  
Help you use specific features like testing tracking links  
Make sure you connect to the right service on our website when we make any changes to the way the website works  
‘Strictly Necessary’ cookies will NOT be used to…

Gather information that could be used to advertise products or services to you  
Remember your preferences or username beyond your current visit  
Accepting these cookies is a condition of using the website, so if you prevent these cookies we can’t guarantee your security or predict how our website will perform during your visit.

Here is a list of the cookies we have defined as ‘strictly necessary’.

indoleads.com cookies:

PHPSESSID  
Cookies provided by 3rd parties:

com does not currently employ any strictly necessary cookies by third parties  
Performance

‘Performance’ cookies collect information about how you use our website e.g. which pages you visit, and if you experience any errors. These cookies don’t collect any information that could identify you – all the information collected is anonymous and is only used to help us improve how our website works, understand what interests our users and measure how effective our  
advertising is.

We use performance cookies to…

Provide statistics on how our website  
is used  
See how effective our adverts are (we don’t  
use this information to target adverts to you when you visit other  
websites  
Provide feedback to partners that one of our  
visitors also visited their website. This can include details of any  
products bought. This lets our partners improve their website, but we don’t  
allow our partners to reuse this information for further advertising  
Help us improve the website by measuring any  
errors that occur  
Test different designs of our website  
Cookies we have defined as ‘Performance’ cookies will NOT be used to…

Remember your preferences or username beyond your current visit  
In some cases, some of these cookies are managed for us by third parties, but we don’t allow the third party to use the cookies for any purpose other than those listed above.

Using our site indicates that you accept the use of ‘Performance’ cookies.

Accepting these cookies is a condition of using the website, so if you prevent them we cannot guarantee how our site will perform for you.

Here is a list of the cookies we have defined as ‘Performance’

indoleads.com cookies

aff_conversions  
__utma  
__utmb  
__utmc  
__utmz  
_pmy_visit  
_pmy_visitor  
is_returning  
Cookies provided by 3rd parties

com does not currently employ any performance cookies provided by third parties  
Functionality

‘Functionality’ cookies are used to provide services or to remember settings to improve your visit.

We use ‘Functionality’ cookies to…

Remember settings you’ve applied such as layout, text size, preferences and colours  
Remember if we’ve already asked you if you want to fill in a survey  
Provide proactive live chat sessions to offer you support or submit a trouble ticket  
Show you when you’re logged in to the website  
Share information with partners to provide a service on our website. The information shared is only to be used to provide the service, product or function and not for any other purpose  
Cookies defined as ‘Functionality’ will not be used to…

20  
Dec

## Thai Airways Affiliate Program has been Launched!

It’s time to fly! Thai Airways is on board! Thai Airways International Public Co,.ltd is a nat 

20  
Dec

## Rotita CPS Offer has Started!

We have a new advertiser on board! Rotita is your global online destination that delivers some of to 

18  
Dec

## Rosewe Offers has Started!

Look what we have here, a new advertiser! Rosewe.com was one of the first online stores and has been
